let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Skippers Transport was formed in",
        answer: "2. 1961",
        choices: [
            "1. Yesterday",
            "2. 1961",
            "3. 1980",
            "4. 1970"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Skippers Transport is a company that specialises in?",
        answer: "3. 3PL Logistics",
        choices: [
            "1. Car transport",
            "2. Aviation",
            "3. 3PL Logistics",
            "4. Take away food"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "3PL stands for?",
        answer: "3. Third party logistics",
        choices: [
            "1. 3rd Person Logistics",
            "2. 3 Party Lingo",
            "3. Third party logistics",
            "4. all of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Which accreditations do Skippers hold?",
        answer: "4. All of the above",
        choices: [
            "1. Australian Trusted Trader",
            "2. HACCP",
            "3. WAHVA",
            "4. All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Please ensure that you ______________________?",
        answer: "1. Always complete documentation in full and accurately",
        choices: [
            "1. Always complete documentation in full and accurately",
            "2. Tell your mates about us",
            "3. Like us on Facebook",
            "4. Come to work most days"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which WAHVA modules are Skippers accredited for",
        answer: "4. All of the above",
        choices: [
            "1. Fatigue Management",
            "2. Dimension and Loading",
            "3. Maintenance",
            "4. All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "The NHVL -Chain of Responsibility (COR) legislation relates to?",
        answer: "4. All of the above",
        choices: [
            "1. Mass and Dimension",
            "2. Fatigue and fitness for duty",
            "3. Load Restraint .",
            "4. All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Conditions of Entry are?",
        answer: "1. A mandatory requirement",
        choices: [
            "1. A mandatory requirement",
            "2. An Option",
            "3. Required only by workers",
            "4. An Annoyance"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "All incidents are?",
        answer: "2. Required to be reported to management to be investigated when safe to do so",
        choices: [
            "1. A hassle",
            "2. Required to be reported to management to be investigated when safe to do so",
            "3. Reported when you feel the need",
            "4. Not to be reported"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Where is one place you can you find information about roles and responsibilities?",
        answer: "3. In responsibility Statements and employment agreements",
        choices: [
            "1. On the internet",
            "2. In the glove box",
            "3. In responsibility Statements and employment agreements",
            "4. Dont know"
        ]
    },






];